ATHM Textile Industry Cloth Labels 6524/003 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Arranged Alphabetically
  - W, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Item 25: Warren Cotton Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Warren, Mass.: Warren Cotton Mills, ca. 1860-1890. Image of cotton plant in center surrounded by red, gold, green and gray frame. 19 x 14 cm.
    - Item 26: Warren Cotton Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Warren, Mass. Warren, Mass.: Warren Cotton Mills, ca. 1860-1890. Gold lettering on red banners; gold and red frame. 16.25 x 20 cm.
    - Item 27: Warren Manufacturing. Compnay, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Warren, R.I.: Warren Mfg. Co., ca. 1850-1900. Gold lettering and center design with the word Hope and an anchor against white background. 5.5 x 6.75 cm. Identical to Item 28, in this folder, except for background color.
    - Item 28: Warren Manufacturing. Compnay, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Item 29: Warwick Colored Flannels, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. Yds. N.p., n.d. Red lettering and frame against cream background. 25.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 30: Warwick Plaids All Wool Filling Warranted Fast Colors, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      No. Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against black- and-white background. 14 x 9 cm.
    - Item 31: Washington, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Trade Mark Registered. Ketterlinus, Lith. Philada. Chromolithograph (?) of woman in Scottish plaid, leaning on shepherd's staff, waving hat in left hand. 11 x 16.5 cm.
    - Item 32: Washington, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Trade Mark Registered. Ketterlinus, Lith. Philada. Chromolithograph (?) of woman in Scottish plaid, wearing hat in outdoor setting. 11 x 16.5 cm.
    - Item 33: Washington, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Trade Mark Registered. N.p., ca. 1800s. Image of woman in Scottish (?) plaid, wearing hat, playing croquet. Upper right-hand corner torn off. 11.5 x 16.5 cm.
    - Item 34: Washington Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and border against white background. 17 x 16 cm.
    - Item 35: Washington Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against cream background; image of young woman holding open book with mill complex in background. 14 x 17.25 cm.
    - Item 36: Washington Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Lawrence, Mass.: Washington Mills, no earlier than 1859. Image depicts George Washington standing beside his horse; image is framed with Washington Mills over it and Lawrence, Mass. beneath it. Originally attached to a skirt; material still attached to
    - Item 37: Balmoral Skirt Washington Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      No. N.p., ca. 1860s. Full-length image of woman in Balmoral skirt, wearing hat; lavender lettering against light tan background. 8.5 x 12.75 cm.
    - Item 38: Premiere qualite, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Lawrence, Mass.: Washington Mills, n.d. Image of American flag on shield in center; black lettering and gold border against white background. 8.5 x 12.75 cm.
    - Item 39: The Bay State Shawl Washington Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Washington Mills Lawrence, Mass. NHSS Reproduction 1976. Gold lettering and border; number 46 stamped in red. Exposition Universelle de MDCCCLXVII A Paris in center. Identical to Item 40, in this folder, except for colors and stamped number. 9.5 x 12
    - Item 40: The Bay State Shawl Washington Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Washington Mills Lawrence, Mass. NHSS Reproduction 1976. Gold lettering and border; number 46 stamped in red. Exposition Universelle de MDCCCLXVII A Paris in center. Identical to Item 39, in this folder, except for colors and stamped number. 9.5 x 12
    - Item 41: Washington Mills Twilled, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Extra Fine All Wool Cloth. N.p., n.d. Image of American flag and shield in center; gold lettering against white background. 13 x 9.5 cm.
    - Item 42: Waterford Improved, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      F.F. Oakley's Lith. Boston. N.p., ca. 1857-1859. Image of mill building by side of falls in center; gold and red lettering and frame against white background. 16 x 19.75 cm.
    - Item 43: Waterloo Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Size 37 x 37 Style. Brown & Warner 69 Leonard St. N.Y. [printer?]. Waterloo, N.Y.: Waterloo Woolen Mfg. Co., ca. 1870s. Image of child wearing shawl in center; black lettering against white background. 5.75 x 7.5 cm.
    - Item 44: Waterville Shawl Warranted All Wool, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      3 40 x 40 Inside the Fringe. Bennington, Vt. Bennington, Vt.: Unknown mill, n.d. Black lettering; number 3 in green; against white background. 6.5 x 8.25 cm.
    - Item 45: Waukaneto Manufacturing Company's Superior Wire Twist Shirtings, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Image of mill building in center; gold lettering and border. 18.5 x 14.25 cm.
    - Item 46: Wauregan Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Wauregan, Conn.: Wauregan Mills, ca. 1853-1899. Image of mill complex in center; blue and gold border. 22 x 16 cm.
    - Item 47: Waverley cambrics, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      42 yds. N.p., n.d. Image of department store/Hunt Building with horse drawn wagon.
    - Item 48: Waverly Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      ___ Yds. Middlesex Bleachery & Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. Black and gold lettering against white oval in center; gold, black, gray and white frame. 10.25 x 13.75 cm.
    - Item 49: Waverly Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Yds. Middlesex Bleachery & Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against cream background. 17 x 20.75 cm.
    - Item 50: Wellington Sleeve LInings, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and border against cream background. 18 x 17 cm.
    - Item 51: Wellington Sleeve LInings, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and border against cream background. 15.75 x 15.75 cm. Copy 2. Label has been trimmed.
    - Item 52: Wellington 4/4 Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; red lettering against white background; blue and gold border. 8.5 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 53: Wessacumcon fine cottons., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Forbes & Co. Lith. Boston. Newburyport, Mass.: Bartlet Steam Mills, ca. 1868-1875. Image of Native American (Wessacumcon?) in center; gold lettering against green banners; green and gold border against white background. 22.25 x 16.25 cm.
    - Item 54: Westminster Colored Flannels, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Yds. Middlesex Bleachery & Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. Red lettering against yellow background. 25.25 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 55: White, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and design against white background; circular shape. 6 x 6 cm.
    - Item 56: White Rock robroy plains, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Yds. White Rock (Westerly), R.I.: White Rock Mfg. Co., n.d. Gold lettering within elaborate red, gold and blue frame against white background. Handwritten recipe for bluing on the reverse. 13.5 x 10 cm.
    - Item 57: Whitestone Prints, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Image of mill complex in center with railroad in foreground; black lettering against white background. 18.25 x 13.25 cm.
    - Item 58: Cinderella flannelette Whittenton Manfacturing Company, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Patt. No. _____ Yds. ____ (Image of queen on throne with subjects) On reverse, a description of cloth. 7 x 10 cm.
    - Item 59: Whittenton blue drills warranted indigo, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      No. ____ Yds. ____. C.H. Crosby, Pr., 3 Water St. Taunton, Mass.: Whittenton Mfg. Co., ca. 1857-1862. Orange lettering and frame against white background. 25 x 20.25 cm.
    - Item 60: Whittenton Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. Taunton, Mass.: Whittenton Mfg. Co., n.d. Black lettering against orange background. Nearly identical to Item 61, in this folder, except for decorative frame. 17 x 21.25 cm.
    - Item 61: Whittenton Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. Taunton, Mass.: Whittenton Mfg. Co., n.d. Black lettering against orange background. Nearly identical to Item 60, in this folder, except for decorative frame. 17 x 21.25 cm.
    - Item 62: Whittenton C Denims, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      No.______ ______Yds. Taunton, Mass.: Whittenton Mfg. Co., n.d. Black lettering against a cream background with a lavender frame around the lettering. 22.5 x 20 cm.
    - Item 63: Whittenton Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Taunton, Mass.: Whittenton Mfg. Co., n.d. Red lettering against light green background, with gold crest in center and gold border. 11.5 x 15 cm.
    - Item 64: Wigans, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and border against deep blue background. 15.75 x 11.5 cm.
    - Item 65: Black Wigans, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering and border against light brown background. 22 x 14.75 cm.
    - Item 66: Extra Heavy Wigans, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Black and gray lettering against white background. 14 x 19.5 cm.
    - Item 67: Improved A A A A Wigans, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Black and red lettering, black border, against white background. 14.25 x 18.5 cm.
    - Item 68: Williamsville Co. Extra Twist Superfine Premium Cottons, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Engraving? Killingly, Conn.: Williamsville Mfg. Co., ca. 1800s. Image of mill building in center. 10.75 x 7.5 cm.
    - Item 69: Winchendon Fine Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Green and red lettering and border against white background. 12.25 x 15 cm.
    - Item 70: Windeclift Fine Silesias, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      ___ Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against white background. 7.5 x 10 cm.
    - Item 71: Winthrop Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      ____ Yds. Ch. H. Crosby, Lith, 46 Water St, Boston. Winthrop, Me.: Winthrop Mills Co., ca. 1870-1872. Gold lettering and image of mill building in center against white background. 14.5 x 18.5 cm.
    - Item 72: Winthrop Mills X X satteen jeans, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      ____ Yds. Winthrop, Me.: Winthrop Mills Co., ca. 1870-1900. Red lettering and gold border against white background. 21.5 x 17.25 cm.
    - Item 73: Wiya-Mawuchiya Inji-Muzurun Tofa [Easy to Use Spinning Machine], Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., ca. 1900s. Probably British for Nigerian trade. Image of bush cat (muzurun tofa) in center climbing tree to escape burning jungle. The adage "Wiya-Mawuchiya" (Difficulty is a thing which passes away) is attributed to the bush cat (muzurun tofa)w
    - Item 74: Wolcott Manufacturing. Co., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Date ____ Quality ____ Weight ____ Temper ____. N.p., ca. 1900s. Black lettering on white background. 4 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 75: Wolfe Falls Co., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Eng. by J.A. Lowell, 228 Washn. St. Boston. Ludlow, Vt.: Wolfe Falls Co., ca. 1862-1865. Cream lettering against light gray oval background, within darker gray frame. 17 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 76: Woodland Mills. Ladies Natural Mixed Merino Vests, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      No. Size Inch. N.p., n.d. Mill complex in center on river with falls; black lettering. 20.5 x 6.5 cm.
    - Item 77: Wool Dyed Satinets, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Double Milled. Perfect Fabric & Finish. No. Yds. N.p., ca. 1800s. Image of buildings at harborside, with sailing ship moored to a wharf with a smaller vessel alongside; other sailing and steam ships in the harbor. 12 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 78: World Wide Fine jeans For All People. Warranted Full Twist, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. Arthur Brown 306 Broadway, N.Y. [printer?]. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against light green background. 12.75 x 17.25 cm.
    - Item 79: Wyoming Fine Cottons, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold and red lettering against white background; red and gold frame. 20 x 26.5 cm.
  - X, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: XXX No. 65. Warranted 36 Yards. Full Count, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Trade Mark. N.p., n.d. Black lettering on gold background. 3.75 x 8 cm.
  - Y, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Yanney Woolen Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Ephratah, N.Y. Case____ Style____ No._____ Yds._____. Ephratah, N.Y.: Levi Yanney, [1870-1900]. Black lettering against white background. 6 x 8.75 cm.
    - Item 2: Yards, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Yards. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering on very thin paper. 18 x 5 cm.
    - Item 3: York Manufacturing Co, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 3)
      No.____ ____ Yds. [Saco, Me.]: York Mfg. Co., n.d. White lettering against red oval background. 12.75 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 4: York Manufacturing Co Nankins, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 3)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. Saco, Me.: York Manufacturing Co., n.d. Patriotic image in center of eagle atop American flags; blue lettering within gold border against white background. 13.5 x 17 cm.
  - Z, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: The pioneer skirt Zanesville Woolen Mfg. Co., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Zanesville, Ohio: Zanesville Woolen Mfg. Co., ca. 1870-1908. Image of woman in colonial garb spinning at a spinning wheel in center. 10.5 x 14 cm.
  - Designs Without Text [folder 1 of 4], Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Parrot, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Color image of a parrot and flowers. No.156, 25 Yds.
    - Item 2: A man and a woman, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Silhouette of another man in background.
    - Item 3: Angel, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      An angel standing in an archway.
    - Item 4: Beehive, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Gold on white.
    - Item 5: Dog, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Color image of a dog standing on grass, with a green border.
    - Item 6: Cameo of a Woman, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 7: Landscape of mill, boats, and water, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 8: Blank label with gold border, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      A gold, oblong, hexagonal frame.
    - Item 9: Blank label with gold border, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Border composed of foliage, people, bugs, an eagle, and other birds.
    - Item 10: Star with gold circle border, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 11: Coat of Arms: Crown, Eagle, Ship, and Bees, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Gold on white. No. ____ ____Yds.
    - Item 12: Window label, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Color, with a man with a dog on the left and a woman with a cat on the right, both embossed in gold.
    - Item 13: Silver and Bronze label, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Shows five different coins with people on them.
    - Item 14: Two women with shawls, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Lithograph, ca. 1860 [trimmed]
    - Item 15: chromo woman, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      ca. 1895
    - Item 16: Gold eagle, lion & ship, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      ca. 1860?
    - Item 17: Blue chromo with central portrait, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      ca. 1880
    - Item 18: Red chromo with central portrait, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      ca. 1880, Kaufmann & Strauss ptrs.
    - Item 19: 9 oz, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 20: Design with a sheep, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 21: Seated woman with a sheep, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Silver with cut-out background.
    - Item 22: Dog, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 23: Oval with lion holding flag in center, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 24: Woman at flax wheel, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Oval, silver with cut-out background.
    - Item 25: Two birds, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      N.p., n.d. No text. Three images depict a parrot (?) within a circle on the left and a bluebird (?) within a circle on the right. In the center is an oval, with an embossed image in gold of flowers. All three circles/ovals are encircled with gold, whi
    - Item 26: An eagle over a lion with flags, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Oval, silver with blue background. No.____ ___Yds.
    - Item 27: A woman with a sheep, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 28: Oblong pattern, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Green and gold on white.
    - Item 29: Woman and child, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Color with a blue and gold border. Also includes a rooster and a chick.
    - Item 30: Steam locomotive ca. 1830, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 31: Farr Alpaca Company - [no print], Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 32: Seated woman with three dogs, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 33: Woman and child with flowers, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 34: Dog, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Gold and green on white.
    - Item 35: Label with eagle, shield and flag with ship., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Patriotic motif [eagle, shield and flags with ship in background and bales in foreground]
    - Item 36: Eagle, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Black on blue. The eagle is holding arrows and an olive branch, with a shield on its chest.
    - Item 37: Camel caravan, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      No text except "Registered trade mark No. 624741." ca. 1900s. Probably British for foreign trade. Colors: green, yellow, red and black. Image: Camel caravan with Arabic riders and trade goods 17 x 22.5 cm.
    - Item 38: 19th century view of mill in Manchester, England, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Malcolm Ross & Sons. Image depicts four- story building with smoking chimney; other buildings on either side. Image in black on yellow background. Manchester, England, n.d. 12.5 x 8.25 cm.
    - Item 39: 19th century view of mill in Manchester, England, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Malcolm Ross & Sons. Image depicts four- story building with smoking chimney; other buildings on either side. Image in black on yellow background. Manchester, England, n.d. 12.5 x 8.25 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 40: Cotton picking, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 5)
      N.p, ca.1890. Multi-colored view of African Americans picking cotton and listening to music; figure sitting on bale playing banjo with another figure leaning on bale. 23.5 X 18 cm.
  - Designs Without Text [folder 2 of 4], Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Cloth labels from ATHM acquistion 0000.453.
  - Designs Without Text [folder 3 of 4], Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Designs Without Text [folder 4 of 4], Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Cloth labels of unknown origin.
  - Talbot Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Duplicates of labels in Box 3, Folder 7.
    - Item 1: Talbot Mills Talbotric, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Talbot Mills Established 1857: Talbotric. Style ____ Shade ____ Case No. ____ Piece No. ____ Yds. ____. Printed on reverse is: No allowance will be made on this piece of goods after it is cut. North Billerica, Mass.: Talbot Mills, ca. 1900-1957. Black
    - Item 2: Talbot Mills Talloura, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Talbot Mills Established 1857: Talloura. Style ____ Shade ____ Case No. ____ Piece No. ____ Yds. ____. Printed on reverse is: No allowance will be made on this piece of goods after it is cut. North Billerica, Mass.: Talbot Mills, ca. 1900-1957. Black l
    - Item 3: Talbot Mills Talvelaine, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Talbot Mills Established 1857: Talvelaine. Style ____ Shade ____ Case No. ____ Piece No. ____ Yds. ____. Printed on reverse is: No allowance will be made on this piece of goods after it is cut. North Billerica, Mass.: Talbot Mills, ca. 1900-1957. Black
    - Item 4: Talbot Mills Talvermist, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Talbot Mills Established 1857: Talvermist. Style ____ Shade ____ Case No. ____ Piece No. ____ Yds. ____. Printed on reverse is: No allowance will be made on this piece of goods after it is cut. North Billerica, Mass.: Talbot Mills, ca. 1900-1957. Black
    - Item 5: Talbot Mills Uniform Cloth, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Talbot Mills Established 1857: Uniform Cloth. Style ____ Shade ____ Case No. ____ Piece No. ____ Yds. ____. Printed on reverse is: No allowance will be made on this piece of goods after it is cut. North Billerica, Mass.: Talbot Mills, ca. 1900-1957. Bl
    - Item 6: Talbot Mills Worsted Finish Dundee, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Talbot Mills Established 1857: Worsted Finish Dundee. Style ____ Shade ____ Case No. ____ Piece No. ____ Yds. ____. Printed on reverse is: No allowance will be made on this piece of goods after it is cut. North Billerica, Mass.: Talbot Mills, ca. 1900-1
  - Printing Blocks, Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Merrimac Mills Aristo-Tex Four-Color Label, Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Coat of Arms with a dogs head (talbot) over a six-bar shield, alternating yellow and blue and red bend, below the shield is a banner with the words "Dum Spiro Spero" [While I Breathe]. Affixed to a manila envelope.
    - Item 2: Merrimac Mills Aristo-Tex Printing Block, Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 1)
      For black ink. Metal die mounted on a wood block.
    - Item 3: Merrimac Mills Aristo-Tex Printing Block, Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 1)
      For blue ink. Metal die mounted on a wood block.
    - Item 4: Merrimac Mills Aristo-Tex Printing Block, Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 1)
      For red ink. Metal die mounted on a wood block.
    - Item 5: Merrimac Mills Aristo-Tex Printing Block, Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 1)
      For yellow ink. Metal die mounted on a wood block.
    - Item 6: Travel-Tex Black and White Label, Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Genuine Travel-Tex with a winged globe trade mark. Affixed to the folder.
    - Item 7: Travel-Tex Printing Block, Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Metal die mounted on metal block.
  - Merrimac Mills, Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Merrimac Mills, Coat of Arms "House of Gaunt", Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 2)
      100% virgin wool worsted. Alfred C. Gaunt & Co. Case____ Style____ No.____ Yards____. On reverse: "No Claims. This piece has been carefully examined at mill, and allowances made for any imperfections. No further allowances will be made. Sponged and Shrunk
    - Item 2: Merrimac Mills, Coat of Arms "House of Gaunt", Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Item 3: Merrimac Mills, Coat of Arms "House of Gaunt", Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Alfred C. Gaunt & Co. Case____ Style____ No.____ Yards____. White background.
    - Item 4: Merrimac Mills, Coat of Arms "House of Gaunt", Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Item 5: Merrimac Mills, Coat of Arms "House of Gaunt", Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Alfred C. Gaunt & Co. Case____ Style____ No.____ Yards____. On reverse: "No Claims. This piece has been carefully examined at mill, and allowances made for any imperfections. No further allowances will be made. Yellow background.
    - Item 6: Merrimac Mills, Coat of Arms "House of Gaunt", Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Item 7: Merrimac Mills, Coat of Arms "House of Gaunt", Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Item 8: Merrimac Mills, Coat of Arms "House of Gaunt", Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 2)
      100% virgin wool worsted. Alfred C. Gaunt & Co. Case____ Style____ No.____ Yards____. On reverse: "No Claims. This piece has been carefully examined at mill, and allowances made for any imperfections. No further allowances will be made. Yellow background.
    - Item 9: Merrimac Mills, Coat of Arms "House of Gaunt", Cloth label (Box 5, Folder 2)